And he had a pretty torrid time
through this whole process.
His wife died, and then he had a stroke.
And this was all the way through pandemic.
So we kind of like Englished
our way through it.
Hello, how are you? Oh, terrible.
OK, well, then shall we look at the draft?
You know, kind of like it was very
kind of it's an interesting friendship,
but it is really entirely based on
this kind of reading each other's work.
And I think this completely
changed my chances of getting my
book published, partly because he
already had a publishing deal and he
pointed me at his publishers and coached
me through writing their proposal
so that I would get my book.